https://seprotec.com/privacy

PRIVACY & COOKIES
PRIVACY POLICY
The objective of this policy is to inform data subjects about the different kinds of processing carried out by this organization via the website that affect your personal data in accordance with the provisions of Organic Act 3/2018 of December 5 on the Protection of Personal Data and the guarantee of digital rights, and with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016.
1. DATA CONTROLLER IDENTIFICATION AND CONTACT INFORMATION
The organization SEPROTEC TRADUCCIÓN E INTERPRETACIÓN, S.L., domiciled at Calle Valle de Alcudia 3, 28232, Las Rozas, Madrid, Spain, bearing Tax ID Number B-82695842, with contact telephone number +34 912048700 and email address pdatos@gruposepro.com and its subsidiaries.
DATA PROTECTION OFFICER
SEGURIDAD Y PRIVACIDAD DE DATOS S.L., domiciled at Avenida Cortes Valencianas, Edificio Géminis Center, 39, 13, C D, 46015, Valencia, Spain, with contact telephone number +34 963122868 and email address: infodpo@forlopd.es
2. PURPOSES OF PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA
VISITORS/BROWSERS OF THE DATA CONTROLLER’S WEBSITE
We will process your personal data provided through our website forms to:
• Deal with requests, complaints and incidents reported through our contact channels or website forms.
• Understand the browser’s behavior on the website so as to detect possible cyberattacks against our website.
• Comply with any legal obligations that apply directly to us and govern our activity.
• Protect and exercise our rights or respond to claims of any kind.
• Send commercial content, where applicable, relating to the goods and/or services involved in our business, and/or news or newsletters linked to our sector.
• Manage and send requested quotes.
• Monitor, administer, and supervise your interactions on the website’s blog/forum.
CLIENTS
We will process your personal data provided through our website forms to:
• Manage our commercial relationship.
• Provide any services you request of us.
• Perform tasks linked to sending and receiving the product/service acquired via the website.
• Take care of administrative tasks, accounting, and tax.
• Deal with requests, complaints, and incidents reported through our contact channels or website forms.
• Understand the browser’s behavior on the website so as to detect possible cyberattacks against our website.
• Send commercial content, where applicable, relating to the goods and/or services involved in our business, and/or news or newsletters linked to our sector.
• Comply with any legal obligations which apply directly to us and govern our activity.
• Protect and exercise our rights or respond to claims of any kind.
SUPPLIERS
We will process your personal data provided through our website forms to:
• Manage our commercial relationship.
• Deal with requests, complaints, and incidents reported through our contact channels or website forms.
• Understand the browser’s behavior on the website so as to detect possible cyberattacks against our website.
• Comply with any legal obligations which apply directly to us and govern our activity.
• Protect and exercise our rights or respond to claims of any kind.
• Send commercial content, where applicable, relating to the goods and/or services involved in our business, and/or news or newsletters linked to our sector.
CANDIDATES FOR JOB OFFERS OR JOB APPLICANTS
We will process your personal data provided through our website forms to:
• Process your application or candidacy.
• Keep you informed of any progress in the recruitment process and of your candidacy within it.
• Understand the browser’s behavior on the website so as to detect possible cyberattacks against our website.
• Protect and exercise our rights or respond to claims of any kind.
• Send information regarding any new job offers we announce that match your profile, provided you have granted us prior authorization to send you such information.
• Transfer your data to companies belonging to GrupoSepro (including all its subsidiaries).
.
3. LAWFUL BASIS FOR DATA PROCESSING
VISITORS/BROWSERS OF THE DATA CONTROLLER’S WEBSITE
• The consent you gave us to process your data for the stated purposes. Refusal to provide your personal data will make it impossible to process them for the aforementioned purposes.
• To comply with any legal obligations applicable to us. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data.
• Our legitimate interest in protecting our image, business and reputation by avoiding any attacks against our website. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data, but will be entitled to exercise the rights set out in section eight of this privacy policy.
CLIENTS
• The execution of an agreement to which the client is party, or the application of pre-contractual measures. Refusal to provide your personal data will make it impossible to process them for the aforementioned purposes.
• The consent you gave us to process your data for purposes other than the development or execution of our existing agreement. Refusal to provide your personal data will make it impossible to process them for the aforementioned purposes.
• To comply with any legal obligations applicable to us. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data.
• Our legitimate interest in protecting our image, business, and reputation by avoiding any attacks against our website. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data, but will be entitled to exercise the rights set out in section eight of this privacy policy.
SUPPLIERS
• The execution of an agreement to which the client is party, or the application of pre-contractual measures. Refusal to provide your personal data will make it impossible to process them for the aforementioned purposes.
• The consent you gave us to process your data for purposes other than the development or execution of our existing agreement. Refusal to provide your personal data will make it impossible to process them for the aforementioned purposes.
• To comply with any legal obligations applicable to us. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data.
• Our legitimate interest in protecting our image, business and progress by avoiding any attacks against our website. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data, but will be entitled to exercise the rights set out in section eight of this privacy policy.
CANDIDATES FOR JOB OFFERS OR JOB APPLICANTS
• The consent you gave us to process your data for the stated purposes. Refusal to provide your personal data will make it impossible to process them for the aforementioned purposes.
• To comply with any legal obligations applicable to us. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data.
• Our legitimate interest in protecting our image, business and progress by avoiding any attacks against our website. In this case, the data subject cannot refuse to allow the processing of their personal data, but will be entitled to exercise the rights set out in section eight of this privacy policy.
4. DATA RETENTION TERMS AND CRITERIA
Any personal data provided will be retained for the necessary length of time to ensure compliance with the purposes for which they were gathered. Once the data are no longer needed for the processing in question, they will be stored and duly blocked such that they can be made available, where applicable, to the authorized Public Administrations, Judges, Courts, or Public Prosecutors, during the legal period in which judicial actions may be pursued arising from the relationship with the client and/or during the legally established retention periods.
If you have sent us your CV, we will retain your data for no longer than one year as of the moment we received it.
Data blockage period:
• SPANISH CIVIL CODE.
From five to fifteen years, as applicable, pursuant to the provisions of Article 1964.2 of the Spanish Civil Code.
• SPANISH CODE OF COMMERCE.
Six years pursuant to the provisions of Article 30 of the Spanish Code of Commerce. This will apply to any commercial information linked to invoices issued or received, receipts, amended invoices, bank documents, etc.
• GENERAL SPANISH TAX LAW.
Four years pursuant to the provisions of Articles 66 to 70 of the Spanish Tax Law. This will apply to any information relating to tax obligations.
5. AUTOMATED DECISIONS AND PROFILING
Neither automated decisions nor profiling are carried out on the website.
6. RECIPIENTS
While your personal data are being processed the organization may transfer said data to third parties in the following cases:
• To courts and tribunals.
• To law enforcement.
• To other authorities or competent public bodies, whenever the data controller is legally obliged to disclose said personal data.
• To banks and financial institutions, when contracted.
7. INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS
The organization carries out international data transfers, which are subjected to suitable protective measures and full guarantees pursuant to data protection regulations. Permission to make said transfers is established in article 49 of the GDPR.
Data are transferred to entities (company’s subsidiaries) in Poland, Switzerland and the USA.
8. RIGHTS
As a data subject, you are informed that you may exercise the following rights free of charge at any time: access, rectification and/or erasure. You may also: request that the processing of your personal data be limited, oppose such processing, request the portability of your data (where technically possible), or withdraw your consent. As applicable, you may ask not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling.
To do so, you may use the forms provided by the organization or send a request to the postal address or email address indicated above. In any case, your request must include a photocopy of your ID card or equivalent document showing proof of identity.
If you feel that your rights have been violated in relation to the protection of your personal data, especially if you are not satisfied regarding the exercise of your rights, you may file a complaint with the pertinent Data Protection Control Authority (in this case, the Spanish Data Protection Agency), through their website: www.aepd.es.
Pursuant to the provisions of Article 21 of Act 34/2002 on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce, if you do not wish to receive information regarding our services, you can unsubscribe by emailing us at pdatos@gruposepro.com and putting “BAJAS” in the subject line..
9. ACCURACY OF DATA
The data subject guarantees that the information provided is real, exact, complete and up-to-date, hereby undertaking to report any changes in the data provided through the channels enabled for this purpose as indicated in point one of this policy. You will be liable for any direct and indirect damages that may result from any breach of this obligation.
If you are providing third-party data, you hereby declare that you have the consent of the data subject and undertake to inform said party of the information contained in this clause, exempting the organization from any liability arising from any failure to comply with this obligation.
COOKIES POLICY
The purpose of this policy is to inform data subjects about the cookies used by this website in accordance with the provisions of Act 34/2002 of July 11 on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce, and with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016.
1. USE OF COOKIES. WHAT ARE COOKIES?
Cookies are files that are downloaded to your computer, smartphone or tablet when you access certain websites. Using cookies entails several advantages for the provision of services in the Information Society, such as:
(a) Improving the browsing experience for website users;
(b) Enabling the user to access the various services offered on the website;
(c) Preventing the user from having to adjust the predefined settings every time they access the website;
(d) Favoring the performance of the website and aiding in the provision of the services provided by previously analyzing the information obtained from the cookies installed.
(e) Allowing the website to perform tasks such as storing and retrieving information about the browsing habits of a user or about their device; depending on the information they contain and the way the computer is used, they can also help to recognize the user.
Most browsers accept cookies as a standard feature. In any case, temporary or memorized cookies can be enabled or disabled in the browser security settings.
Keep in mind that to ensure the best possible browsing experience, you will need to enable cookies, especially technical cookies that are needed to identify you as a registered user every time you access the website.
If you do not wish to receive cookies, please adjust your Internet browser settings to erase them from your computer's hard drive, block them, or alert you before installing them.
2. WHAT TYPES OF COOKIES ARE USED ON THIS WEBSITE?
Cookies used on this website
Following the guidelines of the Spanish Data Protection Agency, we will now proceed to provide details of the use of cookies on this website in order to offer you as much information as possible.
Proprietary cookies:
These cookies are sent to the user’s device from a system or domain managed by the cookie editor, which is also used to provide the service requested by the user.
Here is a list of the ones we use:
NAME
PROVIDER
PURPOSE
EXPIRATION
TYPE
PHPSESSID
seprotec.com
Preserves the status of the user in every website request.
Session
HTTP
GDPR
seprotec.com
Stores the status of the user’s acceptance of cookies for the current domain.
Session
HTTP
Third-party cookies:
These cookies are sent to the user’s device from a system or domain that is not managed by the editor, but by another entity that processes the data obtained from these cookies.
Here is a list of the ones we use:
NAME
PROVIDER
PURPOSE
EXPIRATION
TYPE
_ga [x2]
Google Tag Manager
Records a unique identifier which is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
2 years
HTTP
_gat [x2]
Used by Google Analytics to control the number of requests.
1 day
HTTP
_gid [x2]
Google Tag Manager
Records a unique identifier which is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
1 day
HTTP
SEPROTEC TRADUCCIÓN E INTERPRETACIÓN, S.L. and its subsidiaries take no responsibility in any case for the content or veracity of third-party policies and/or conditions of use and privacy, including those to which links are provided in this policy.
3. CONSENT
In relation to the use of the above-mentioned cookies on this website, the user hereby authorizes and consents to the use thereof as follows: When accessing the website, the user will see a message informing them that the website uses cookies. The user can choose whether or not to accept the use thereof by clicking on the ‘accept’/’accept all’ button and adjusting their preferences in the settings panel and/or on the browser. If the user does not press accept, does not adjust their browser settings or the settings in the panel, and continues to use the SEPROTEC TRADUCCIÓN E INTERPRETACIÓN, S.L. and its subsidiaries’ website, using its services, they will be considered to have accepted the use of the necessary cookies on this website.
4. HOW TO BLOCK OR DELETE INSTALLED COOKIES
You can allow, block or delete the cookies installed on your computer by adjusting your browser settings. Information on how to do that for the most common browsers can be found on the links included below:
Explorer
Microsoft Edge
Chrome
Firefox
Safari
Opera
Please be aware, however, that disabling any cookies may prevent or hinder browsing or the provision of the services offered on the website.
5. MODIFICATIONS
This cookie policy may be modified in accordance with established legal requirements and/or for the purpose of adapting said policy to instructions issued by the Spanish Data Protection Agency.
Users are, therefore, advised to periodically visit our cookie policy.
When significant changes occur in this policy, we will inform users of such changes through a notice on our website, insofar as possible.
If you have any questions regarding this cookie policy, please contact SEPROTEC TRADUCCIÓN E INTERPRETACIÓN, S.L. by emailing us at: pdatos@gruposepro.com
